<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <TipSetDef>
    <defName>StorytimeTips</defName>
    <tips>
      <li TKey="HelpfulAdviceFromGod1">"If you need to look at a damn wiki to understand this mod, you shouldn't be playing it." -God</li>	
      <li TKey="HelpfulAdviceFromGod2">Turtleshroom is no longer welcome here.</li>	
      <li TKey="HelpfulAdviceFromGod3">I want to have gay sex while developing this mod.</li>	
      <li TKey="HelpfulAdviceFromGod4">I want to have gay sex with Jonah.</li>	
	  
      <li TKey="Quote1">Most racist things are true.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote2">The first step to winning is admitting that you suck.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote3">Shhh...its vision is based off of sight.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote4">We should car bomb friendlies.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote5">Don't talk.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote6">rate limited try later.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote7">How would a car do the hitler salute?</li>
      <li TKey="Quote8">If you eat one more burrito I'm putting you in the ground.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote9">I spit on old people for fun.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote10">What is the half-life of a coconut?</li>
      <li TKey="Quote11">Wanna buy a gun?</li>
      <li TKey="Quote12">Dimensions are a lot like old people.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote13">I have long since purged myself of any emotion but animal rage.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote14">"Let's bomb the Hogwarts Express" said Harry.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote15">The babies look like mushrooms.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote16">People generally aren't that valuable compared to items.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote17">I wouldn't spit on you if you were dying.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote18">Mike Pence serves Tom Bombadil.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote19">The point is, is that 5 years ago in September there was something else out there...</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote20">Why create what you can steal?</li>
      <li TKey="Quote21">Roots are in the dirt where they belong.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote22">I am the missing arm.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote23">Pickle is my spirit animal.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote24">Tanner feeds on human suffering.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote25">I have level one moon jukes.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote26">Just because they talk doesn't mean they feel pain.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote27">Let's go pistol-whip Tanner with a BB Gun.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote28">Jonah has officially had his racist status revoked as of 9:20 PM, July 17, 2013.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote29">People generally aren't that valuable compared to items.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote30">I am going to cut my own legs off so I can run at peak efficiency.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote31">Let's lynch a pikmin.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote32">I want to sucker punch babies.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote33">Tanner is a master of gaslighting.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote34">I commit warcrimes based on my feelings on the time, not political ideology.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote35">I see something chicken-shaped and I punch it.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote36">I'm too busy using my radical freedom on things that aren't stupid to do that.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote37">It's like giving tattoos to an ant.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote38">I am being DDOSed by Santa.</li>
      <li TKey="Quote39">I think I could last in boiling water longer than a lobster.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote40">Beekeeping is one of my hobbies, you know.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote41">Where do I file my application to become registered as a terrorist organization?</li>
      <li TKey="Quote42">It's bug season.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote43">It's said that bugs in the vicinity of my apartment have 30% higher rates of cancer even half a century later.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote44">I am the Grenade Brother.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote45">One giant's ice cream is another Alphonse's gain.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote46">I'm gonna jump off!</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote47">Mao can transmute a maggot into a worm.</li>	  
	  <li TKey="Quote48">You have to like something to care about it.</li>
	  <li TKey="Quote49">Yeah, my raptor fucks.</li>  
	  <li TKey="Quote50">The market is wide open for a Cao Cao sitcom.</li>  
	  <li TKey="Quote51">"I am not an ant" - Known Ant</li>  
	  <li TKey="Quote52">"Taters- Boil 'em, freeze 'em, stick 'em up your ass." - Jonah</li>  
	  <li TKey="Quote53">Do duppies even have genders?</li>  
	  <li TKey="Quote54">I want a crystal that cures my erectile dysfunction.</li> 
	  <li TKey="Quote55">Yoda must punish Dobby's asshole.</li> 	  
	  <li TKey="Quote56">If you could go back in time and kill baby Donald Duck, would you?</li> 	 
      <li TKey="Quote57">Not a red error in sight, just tall humans living in the moment.</li> 	 
	  <li TKey="Quote58">What is Carl Douglas' egg color?</li> 	 
	  <li TKey="Quote59">You lack the self-confidence to be a good terrorist.</li> 	 
	  <li TKey="Quote60">We need to get more quotes out there, but we can't force it.</li> 	 	 
    </tips>
  </TipSetDef>
</Defs>